<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Codigo</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>

    <string name="codigo_bio">Hello!
        This is the Group Portfolio Project for the Android Pursuit Group, Codigo.
        Our Group consists of 4 members:\n
        Our Demo lead, Luis Jimenez;
        Tech lead, Michell Vargas;
        Design lead, Jessica Perez-Valle;
        and Project manager, Gerardo Jimenez.
        Our name is a callback to our hispanic roots and our commitment to learning to code.</string>
    <string name="bio_text_jess">
        Born April 21, 1990 in Cuernavaca, Morelos, Mexico; middle child of three girls.\n
        Jessica migrated to the United Stated at the age of 9 years old. She is currently a DACA
        recipient, and \"DREAMER\" in all aspects.\n Jessica found herself lost for some time; unsure
        of her future. She joined Pursuit in the fall of 2018 in hopes of making a change in her life.
        Her current goal is to be the best example to her daughter, Sadie, and show her that it is
        never to late to accomplish your goals.\n Jessica now finds herself motivated and excited about
        the next phase in her life. \n Bio to be continued...
       </string>
    <string name="bio_text_geo">Gerardo Jimenez is a Android Development Fellow at Pursuit who carries
    with him a passion for learning about the latest in technology and what it means for the quality
    of life of others in both the near and distant future. Those who know him call him Geo and he is a
    lover of black coffee, Blizzard games, comic books, and the scientific method. Geo is a proud son
    of Colombian immigrants, he shows his pride by engaging with the younger members of his family in
    Spanish, teaching them his mothers recipes, and reminding them that it is important to remember
    their family history. His hope is to be a role model to his nieces and nephews so that they might
    chase their dreams and find their own success.</string>
    <string name="bio_text_michell">Bio goes here...</string>
    <string name="bio_text_luis">Luis is awesome..nuff said</string>
    <string name="name_jess">Jessica</string>
    <string name="name_michell">Michell</string>
    <string name="name_geo">Gerardo</string>
    <string name="name_luis">Luis</string>
    <string name="popup_menu_link_one">Project One</string>
    <string name="popup_menu_link_two">Project Two</string>
    <string name="popup_menu_link_three">Project Three</string>
    <string name="geo_title">Geo</string>
    <string name="jessica_title">Jessica</string>
    <string name="luis_title">Luis</string>
    <string name="michell_title">Michell</string>
    <string name="codigo">Codigo</string>
    <string name="my_header_title">Meet the team:</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer">Nav Drawer</string>
    <string name="git_dialog_title">"Checkout Some Projects</string>
    <string name="incomplete_feature_toast">Feature Not Yet Implemented</string>
    <string name="main_pic_description">Team Codigo Working, like they do.</string>
</resources>
